# Zeina Hesham El-Adawy FOREIGN LANGUAGES AND TRANSLATION

E-mail: xeina.hesham@gmail.com

phone: +201094399368

adress: first Settlement, El Banafseg 9, New cairo, Egypt

#### **Education**

Foreign Languages and Translation

Sep 2018 – Jun 2022

Misr university for science & Technology, Cairo

**English department** 

Second language: German

•

# **Employment**

pharmacist assistant

May 2019 - Aug 2019

pharmacy

Arabic teacher

May 2021 - Apr 2022

Zamzam, online

Arabic teacher Ustadhy, online

Apr 2022 - present

### **Courses**

English, amideast Jul 2018

Japanese, kadol Sep 2020

ICDL, M.U.S.T Sep 2021 – Dec 2021

Japanese, The Japan Foundation Sep 2021 – present

## **Profile**

Compassionate, creative and effective Teacher with valuable experience in classroom administration, professional development and project planning. Equipped with extensive background in versatile education environments. Student-centric instructor, academic facilitator and motivational coach. Competent at performing independently or as member of teaching team. Well-versed in classroom and online technologies.

Personal information

date of birth July 19<sup>th</sup>, 2000

gender female

### **Skills**

**Excellent writing skills** 

Teacher collaboration

Test and quiz creation

Attention to detail Good organization

Learning style assessment

**Lesson Planning** 

**Records Maintenance** 

#### **Languages**

Arabic

Native, fluent

English

Fluent

Japanese

Good

Deutsch

Moderate